{
  "quiz_name": "Adobe Campaign Business Practitioner",
  "topics" :[
    {"key": "Campaign Design and Management", "percent":  15},
    {"key": "Delivery Management", "percent":  31}, 
    {"key": "Workflow Management", "percent": 25}, 
    {"key": "Administration", "percent":  12}, 
    {"key": "Using Email Designer", "percent":  7}, 
    {"key": "Using Reports", "percent": 10} 

  ],
  "percentageCorrectForPassingScore": 70, 
  "quiz_questions": [
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which three aspects of an A/B test should a Practitioner use Adobe Campaign to configure? ","presented_options":["indicators","sample size","confidence level","response delay"],"correct_options":["indicators","sample size","response delay"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The number of records out of union is less than intended. Which conclusion should be made? ","presented_options":["The target is dropping exclusions.","The target populations are NOT mutually exclusive.","The target is dropping inactive records.","The target schemas are NOT the same."],"correct_options":["The target populations are NOT mutually exclusive."],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the advantage of using a string delimiter in the extraction file format? ","presented_options":["results in a smaller file","allows the use of Unicode values","allows the use of the column separator in string values","speeds up the generation of the file"],"correct_options":["allows the use of the column separator in string values"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How would you send a proof to the 'Holiday Marketing Team' list for approvals? ","presented_options":["Select the list from the send a Proof menu","You cannot send the proof to the lists","Enter the email addressed into the \"To:\" line","Select the email addresses from the recipient table"],"correct_options":["Select the email addresses from the recipient table"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Why might a Practitioner change the filtering dimension in a query? ","presented_options":["to make the query more efficient","to return records other than Recipients","to execute a left outer join","to specify filtering conditions"],"correct_options":["to specify filtering conditions"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which workflow activity should be used to export data? ","presented_options":["Extract file","List update","Update data","Data download"],"correct_options":["Extract file"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A Practitioner's team learns that Gmail has modified its spam filtering criteria.  How should the Practitioner use the client console to obtain the percentage of users that have been affected by this change?.","presented_options":["use \"Counters\" within \"Platform\" selection in the Navigation hierarchy","use \"Aggregates\" functionality within Production - Objects created automatically","filter the Recipient dataset based on emails that contain the string \"gmail\" and divide by total number of Recipients","export the list of the recipients to Excel and create a formula to calculate the required percentage"],"correct_options":["filter the Recipient dataset based on emails that contain the string \"gmail\" and divide by total number of Recipients"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What happens when an email delivery is sent without a subject line?","presented_options":["The Delivery Label is used as the subject line","The delivery fails to save","The delivery preparation fails","The campaign creator receives a delivery notification"],"correct_options":["The delivery preparation fails"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Following Campaign Standard default control rules, what should always be included in the body copy of an email delivery?","presented_options":["Preheader","Unsubscribe Link","Subject Line","Personalizaed greetings"],"correct_options":["Unsubscribe Link"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which field is used to determine the profile's variant in a multilingual delivery in an out-of-the-box configuration?","presented_options":["Preferred Language","Country","Geography","Location"],"correct_options":["Preferred Language"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How can you verify that the email content is displayed correctly across different email clients?","presented_options":["Include a trap test profile","Use the Preview feature","Send an Email rendering test email","Send a Proof test email"],"correct_options":["Send an Email rendering test email"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Some emails addresses are shared by multiple profiles. During a delivery, the business team requires to only send one message per email address regardless of the number of profiles sharing the email address. Where is the best location for suuch a business requirement to exist?","presented_options":["In the marketing workflow using an Exclusion activity","As a typology rule during message preparation","Through the data loading process","In the marketing workflow using a Query activity"],"correct_options":["As a typology rule during message preparation"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the cause of this email delivery failure error message, 'The recipient no longer wants to be contacted'?","presented_options":["The address is not specified.","The address is expired.","The address is blacklisted.","The address is not defined."],"correct_options":["The address is blacklisted."],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Practice Exam","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you need to upload a file that contains data exported from a CRM system, which of the following workflow activities would you use to upload the file into Campaign? ","presented_options":["Update data","Transfer file","Reconciliation","Load file"],"correct_options":["Transfer file"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following options is the more common and recommended approach for exporting data in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Generic Export Job","List views","Export Template","Workflows"],"correct_options":["Workflows"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The import template method is recommended when the marketer plans to regularly import profile data and the import job requirements are varied. True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following data management activities would you use to match source data, data that has been imported into Campaign, with existing records in Campaign? ","presented_options":["Transfer file","Extract file","Load file","Reconciliation"],"correct_options":["Reconciliation"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To perform a mass update of data in the Adobe Campaign database, a user would select which of the following data management workflow activities? ","presented_options":["Extract file","Reconciliation","Load file","Update data"],"correct_options":["Update data"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Load file activity allows you to complete which of the following use case? ","presented_options":["Identify links to the source data, based on attributes","Export data from a file to use in the workflow","Extract data into the format of a file","Import data from a file to use in the workflow"],"correct_options":["Import data from a file to use in the workflow"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"In Campaign, you can import data using a workflow, or using an import template. A workflow offers a mechanism to import transactions, households, or profiles by using the data management activities. True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In a workflow, there are six Data Management activities that are available to configure the importing and expoting of data; identify the activities. Select the three correct answers.","presented_options":["Update data and subscription services","Save audience and deduplication","Transfer file and Extract file","Reconciliation and Load file"],"correct_options":["Update data and subscription services","Transfer file and Extract file","Reconciliation and Load file"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are options to export data in Adobe Campaign Standard? Select the two correct answers. ","presented_options":["Generic Export Job","List views","Workflows","Export Template"],"correct_options":["List views","Workflows"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Why is it important that the importing data workflow be configured and executed by an advanced user who knows how to properly configure Campaign's data structure? Select the two correct answers.","presented_options":["To avoid potential corruption of the data model","To avoid potential corruption of data","To avoid deleting existing data","To avoid unauthorized modifications to the data model"],"correct_options":["To avoid potential corruption of the data model","To avoid deleting existing data"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following options offers a quick method for exporting a file to the local system?","presented_options":["Export Template","Workflows","List views","Generic Export Job"],"correct_options":["List views"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are benefits of the import template? Select the two correct answers.","presented_options":["A simplified interface for importing profile data","A pre-configured workflow for importing transaction data","A simplified interface for importing transaction data","A pre-configured workflow for importing profile data"],"correct_options":["A simplified interface for importing profile data","A pre-configured workflow for importing profile data"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Subscription Services activity allows you to subscribe or unsubscribe a mass list of profiles to a Campaign service. True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"ACS: Technical Foundations for BP (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Top Bar menu in the ACS interface and the ACS Home page have the same options? True or false?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the function of the Solution Picker option in the Top Bar menu?","presented_options":["It allows users to navigate to other Adobe Experience Cloud solutions directly from ACS","It allows users to select assets from other Adobe Creative Cloud solutions directly from ACS","It allows users to select profiles from other Adobe Experience Cloud solutions directly from ACS"],"correct_options":["It allows users to navigate to other Adobe Experience Cloud solutions directly from ACS"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Profiles page gives you an option to toggle between list and card view. True or false?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"You are in the Marketing Activities section of the ACS interface. What are the different Search options available to you on this screen?","presented_options":["Keyword","Start and End date","Activity Type","Execution Status","Label","Email Address"],"correct_options":["Keyword","Start and End date","Execution Status","Activity Type"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which menu is available on every screen of ACS? ","presented_options":["The Quick Actions Menu","The Advanced menu","The Action Bar menu","The Top Bar menu"],"correct_options":["The Top Bar menu"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"All users have the same options available in the ACS user interface. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How are profiles most commonly created in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["By building profiles directly in Adobe Campaign Standard UI","By importing profiles in batches using an import workflow","By using the Campaign API through a web application"],"correct_options":["By importing profiles in batches using an import workflow"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The list of profiles contained in a Query audience is fixed. The list is generated the first time the Query is used, and never recomputed. ?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which type of profile would you use to send proofs in ACS? ","presented_options":["Active profile","Custom profile","Test profile","Trap profile"],"correct_options":["Test profile"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which feature of ACS allows you to create a segment of targeted profiles and use it in multiple campaigns?","presented_options":["Audiences","Integrated customer profiles","Test profiles"],"correct_options":["Audiences"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Proofs are sent exclusively to test profiles?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What can you use to personalize content in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Custom templates","Personalization fields","Content fragments","Dynamic content"],"correct_options":["Personalization fields","Dynamic content"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements is true regarding using dynamic content in an email?","presented_options":["You cannot define the order of priority in which the condition will be applied","You can define only two or three variants of dynamic content","You can confiure the email to dynamically display different content"],"correct_options":["You can confiure the email to dynamically display different content"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true in regarding the target breakdown parameter in Adobe Campaign Standard? ","presented_options":["Profiles targeted by each variant are chosen randomly","The remaining target size can be defined manually","Parameter can be set automatically or manually","Each variant can have a different size"],"correct_options":["Profiles targeted by each variant are chosen randomly","Parameter can be set automatically or manually"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the different email types in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Single-send","A/B test","One-to-Many","Recurring"],"correct_options":["Single-send","A/B test","Recurring"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which types of marketing activities can a campaign contain? ","presented_options":["Workflows","Landing pages","Services","SMS deliveries","Email deliveries","Programs"],"correct_options":["Workflows","Landing pages","SMS deliveries","Email deliveries"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true regarding the Timeline feature in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["It displays programs chronologically between their start date and end dates","It cannot be accessed from the Home Page","It displays workflows","It indicates the current date by using a blue vertical line"],"correct_options":["It displays programs chronologically between their start date and end dates","It indicates the current date by using a blue vertical line"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true regarding content fragments in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["You cannot edit content fragments within the email content","You can insert personalization inside a content fragment","Content fragments are locked by default","Content fragments are reusable components"],"correct_options":["Content fragments are locked by default","Content fragments are reusable components"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which A/B parameters can you define in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Number of variants","Audience breakdown","Delivery method","Test duration","Winning strategy"],"correct_options":["Number of variants","Test duration","Winning strategy"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Adobe Campaign Standard allows you to insert links into the content of an email message. Which link types are available in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Dynamic link","Internal link","External link","Unsubscription link","Subscription link","Landing page"],"correct_options":["External link","Unsubscription link","Subscription link","Landing page"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What do programs and campaigns in Adobe Campaign Standard let you do?","presented_options":["Plan and organize marketing campaigns","Transfer files within campaigns","Generate reports on programs and campaigns","Reuse marketing activities within the same campaign or program","Regroup all the different marketing activities linked to a campaign"],"correct_options":["Plan and organize marketing campaigns","Generate reports on programs and campaigns","Regroup all the different marketing activities linked to a campaign"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are content blocks available within Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Welcome message","Brand logo","Brand URL","Default sender name","Link to mirror page","Loyalty program"],"correct_options":["Brand logo","Default sender name","Link to mirror page"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When you include links in your emails, Adobe Campaign Standard provides URL tracking. Which of the following statements are true regarding tracked URLs?","presented_options":["Mirror page URL and unsubscription links are included in the tracked URLs","Tracking is not activated by default","Tracking can be activated or deactivated for each URL","Tracking is available only for email deliveries","Tracking is activated by deafault in th email properties"],"correct_options":["Tracking can be activated or deactivated for each URL","Tracking is available only for email deliveries","Tracking is activated by deafault in th email properties"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How are Segments and Time components different in an ACS Freeform table?","presented_options":["Segments filter data for a specified dimension whereas the Time components filter data for the specified range","Segments filter the data for a specified range, whereas Time adds an additional dimension to break down the data","Segments add an additional dimension to break down the data, whereas Time filters data for a selected period"],"correct_options":["Segments filter the data for a specified range, whereas Time adds an additional dimension to break down the data"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which time period is selected by default when you create a new project?","presented_options":["Last 60 days","Last 30 days","Last full 6 months","This month"],"correct_options":["This month"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following is a dynamic report?","presented_options":["Service summary report","Fatigue rules summary report","Hot clicks report","Delivery summary report"],"correct_options":["Delivery summary report"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are dimensions that can be added to your report?","presented_options":["Campaign","Device","Click","Profile","Blacklisted","Opens"],"correct_options":["Campaign","Device","Profile"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are the different levels of reports available in ACS?","presented_options":["Program, Campaign, Hot Clicks, and Instance","Program, Campaign, Delivery, and Instance","Program, Campaign, Email rendering, and Instance"],"correct_options":["Program, Campaign, Delivery, and Instance"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What components do you need to add to the panel to build a Freeform table?","presented_options":["Filters","Logs","Metrics","Dimensions"],"correct_options":["Metrics","Dimensions"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Why should you lock the data source settings of a visualization in the ACS Reporting interface?","presented_options":["To prevent the visualization from changing when a different mode is selected","To prevent the visualization from being deleted","To prevent data from changing when a different cell is selected"],"correct_options":["To prevent data from changing when a different cell is selected"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How are custom dynamic reports distinguished from the out-of-the-box reports in the ACS Reports interface?","presented_options":["For out-of-the-box reports, the attribute Custom is set to \"false\"","For custom reports, the attribute Custom is set to \"true\"","For custom reports, the attribute Custom is set to \"true\"","Out-of-the-box reports have a blue icon","Custom reports have a blue icon"],"correct_options":["Custom reports have a blue icon"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are broad logs in ACS?","presented_options":["The events that occur when a report is shared","The events that occur when a message is delivered","The events that occur when an email delivery is opened by a profile","The events that occur when a message is sent"],"correct_options":["The events that occur when a message is sent"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Share feature in ACS reports allows you to share reports with anyone, inside or outside your Campaign instance. It will create a PDF version of the report and share the report by email to any email addresses specified","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following comprise a dynamic report?","presented_options":["Filters","Freeform table","Components","Panel","Canvas"],"correct_options":["Freeform table","Components","Panel"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can add multiple segments to a report instance","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"All the components available to build a Freeform table in ACS are specific to Service summary data","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"How does Adobe Campaign Standard support multilingual campaigns?","presented_options":["Allows you deliver multi languages but to only report on the effectiveness of a delivery only the default language","Provides the capability to create multilingual content in a unified solution","Provides the capability to create content on multiple platforms","Provides the ability to scale multilingual campaigns across Email, Push, and SMS Channels","Report on effectiveness of delivery across all languages"],"correct_options":["Provides the capability to create multilingual content in a unified solution","Provides the ability to scale multilingual campaigns across Email, Push, and SMS Channels","Report on effectiveness of delivery across all languages"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which Trap Insertion Mode will you select to insert traps to your direct mail delivery, such that the trap is not obvious to the direct mail delivery service provider?","presented_options":["At the end of the file","Respect the sort order defined in the file","At the start of the file"],"correct_options":["Respect the sort order defined in the file"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What type of a campaign channel is direct mail?","presented_options":["Offline channel","Pull channel","Push channel","Online channel"],"correct_options":["Offline channel"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What type of encoding restricts the length of an SMS to 160 characters?","presented_options":["Unicode encoding","GSM encoding","ACSII encoding"],"correct_options":["GSM encoding"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is used to identify the languages supported in a multilingual delivery?","presented_options":["Variables","Variants","Preferences","Options"],"correct_options":["Variants"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What type of direct mail delivery in ACS will allow you to send a campaign multiple times to target profiles?","presented_options":["Continuous direct mail delivery","Multi-send direct mail delivery","Single-send direct mail delivery","Recurring direct mail delivery"],"correct_options":["Recurring direct mail delivery"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You are configuring a set of profiles to be targeted through direct mail. Which field must be checked in the profiles and test profiles for them to be targeted in direct mail campaigns?","presented_options":["Direct mail specified","Zip/Postcode","Address","Address Specified"],"correct_options":["Address Specified"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What steps in the SMS creation process are guided by the SMS creation wizard?","presented_options":["Create SMS delivery","Set properties","Design the content","Prepare and send","Select type","Specify audience"],"correct_options":["Set properties","Design the content","Select type","Specify audience"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following features can be inserted into the content of a landing page?","presented_options":["Subscription link","JavaScript","Personalization fields","Text version of the landing page","Audience","Content blocks"],"correct_options":["Subscription link","Personalization fields","Content blocks"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where can you see which services a profile is currently subscribed to?","presented_options":["In the Event list of the service","In the Subscriptions tab of the profiles properties","In the Subscriptions tab of the service","In the Event list of the profile record"],"correct_options":["In the Subscriptions tab of the profiles properties"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What feature of ACS would you use to create and manage newsletters?","presented_options":["Audiences","Landing pages","Services","Transactional messages"],"correct_options":["Services"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are the four stages of a landing page lifecycle in ACS?","presented_options":["Creation/Development > Test > Publication > Expiration/Depublication","Creation/Editing > Test > Publication > Expiration/Depublication","Creation > Editing > Test > Publication/Depublication"],"correct_options":["Creation/Editing > Test > Publication > Expiration/Depublication"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which landing page allows a profile to opt out from all deliveries?","presented_options":["Subscription","Profile acquisition","Blacklist","Unsubscription"],"correct_options":["Blacklist"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blanks. Landing pages are _________ that manage subscriptions to a service.","presented_options":["Services","Online forms","Offline forms"],"correct_options":["Online forms"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which landing page template would you use to create a new profile, or update an existing one?","presented_options":["Edit profile","Subscription","Profile acquisition","Create profile"],"correct_options":["Profile acquisition"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which service property sends transactional messages to profiles to confirm services?","presented_options":["Default subscription landing pages","Send messages","Confirmation messages"],"correct_options":["Confirmation messages"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the different ways to promote a service using Adobe Campaign Standard? Select the two correct answers?","presented_options":["On a website","Via email","Via Push Notification","Via SMS"],"correct_options":["On a website","Via email"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the four types of landing pages supported by ACS? Select the four correct answers.","presented_options":["Profile survey","Subscription","Product detail","Event registration","Unsubscription","Profile acquisition","BlackList"],"correct_options":["Subscription","Unsubscription","Profile acquisition","BlackList"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following allows you to select a block in the content editor of a landing page?","presented_options":["The show source feature","HTML breadcrumb","The show blocks feature"],"correct_options":["HTML breadcrumb"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following options will you use to test a landing page?","presented_options":["Audience","Proof Test profile","Profile","Email Rendering Test Profile"],"correct_options":["Profile"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the viewable tabs in the Service Dashboard? Select the two correct answers.","presented_options":["Event List","Subscriptions","Service Summary","Subscription History"],"correct_options":["Subscriptions","Subscription History"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How can you create a generic subscription/unsubscription landing page to use with multiple services? ","presented_options":["By selecting the Service from the URL option","By selecting the Specific service option","By selecting the Subscribe service option","By selecting the Authorize visitor identification via URL parameters option"],"correct_options":["By selecting the Service from the URL option"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the three pages of a landing page?","presented_options":["Confirmation page","Main landing page","Home page","Error page","Authentication page","Exception page"],"correct_options":["Confirmation page","Main landing page","Error page"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Overview (OD)","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What activities can a functional administrator perform on a technical workflow?","presented_options":["Enable and Disable","Restart and Pause","Modify and Pause","Restart and Modify"],"correct_options":["Restart and Pause"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which workflow statuses occur before the workflow is started?","presented_options":["Restart","Finished","Warning","In progress","Erroneous","Editing"],"correct_options":["In progress","Editing"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which activities are included in the Targeting Palette for Workflow Activities?","presented_options":["Enrichment","External signal","Deduplication","Intersection","Reconciliation","Update Data"],"correct_options":["Enrichment","Deduplication","Intersection"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In the Execution palette, which activity is used to create multiple outbound transitions to execute several activities concurrently?","presented_options":["External signal","AND-join","Fork","Scheduler"],"correct_options":["Fork"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you're going to modify a workflow without any risk, the workflow must be in which status?","presented_options":["In progress (blue)","Finished (green)","Warning (yellow)","Editing (gray)"],"correct_options":["Editing (gray)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What connects the activities in a workflow? ","presented_options":["Chanels","The Action Bar","Transitions","Segmentation"],"correct_options":["Transitions"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following options are targeting activities in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Reconciliation","Query","Scheduler","Read Audience"],"correct_options":["Query","Read Audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You need to segment customers based on their total spend amount and have 1000 target customers per segment. Which segmentation type should you use?","presented_options":["Exclude segment from population","Filter and limit segment population","Filter initial population","Limit segment population"],"correct_options":["Filter and limit segment population"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To send specialized offers, you need to segment customer into specific groups using existing customer data. Which resource type should you use to perform segmentation on existing data?","presented_options":["Temporary resource","Database resource","Workflow resource","Scheduled resource"],"correct_options":["Database resource"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements about segmenting data using workflows in Adobe Campaign Standard is true?","presented_options":["You can create up to 5 segments in a segmentation activity","You can place a segmentation activity in a workflow before the targeting activities, such as a query","You can select database or temporary resource types to perform segmentation","You can create only one segment"],"correct_options":["You can select database or temporary resource types to perform segmentation"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"After which activity types should a segmentation activity be placed?","presented_options":["Channel","Targeting","Scheduler","Execution"],"correct_options":["Targeting"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the resource types available in Campaign Standard to perform segmentation? ","presented_options":["Temporary resource","Recurring resource","Workflow resource","Database resource"],"correct_options":["Temporary resource","Database resource"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true regarding segmentation?","presented_options":["You can create one or more segments from a population","You must perform the segmentation activity before other targeting activities","You can select the resource type to perform segmentation","You cannot assign a code to a segment"],"correct_options":["You can create one or more segments from a population","You can select the resource type to perform segmentation"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Singe Answer","question_text":"To send specialized offers to the right customes, you need to segment the customers based on their preferred channel. Which segmentaton type should you use?","presented_options":["Filter initial population","Exclude segment from population","Limit segment population","Filter and limit segment population"],"correct_options":["Filter initial population"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements is true about the Create a new audience option?","presented_options":["It creates a unique audience only the first time the workflow is executed","It creates a unique audience by replacing the old data with the latest data","It creates a unique audience every time the workflow is executed","It creates a new audience only if the audfience does not already exist"],"correct_options":["It creates a unique audience every time the workflow is executed"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which combination of settings would you choose to create an audience using a workflow with customer data imported daily from a file and the new data appended to the existing data?","presented_options":["Update an existing audience and Replace audience content with new data","Create or update an audience and Complete audience with new data","Create or update an audience and Replace audience content with new data","Create a new audience and Complete audience with new data"],"correct_options":["Create or update an audience and Complete audience with new data"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which activity updates an existing audience or creates a new audience from the population computed in a workflow","presented_options":["Targeting","Segmentation","Save audience","Execution"],"correct_options":["Save audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When you're enriching data using aggregates, which of the following statements is true about defining a filter?","presented_options":["A filter is required, or the workflow will fail when it reaches the corresponding activity","If you do not define a filter, all the data will show","A filter is used only when an initial query is not configured","If you do not define a filter, only the data of the initial query will show"],"correct_options":["If you do not define a filter, all the data will show"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following calculates values from the fields of the targeting dimension or from the fields of dimensions linked to the targeting dimension?","presented_options":["Database","Collections","Simple data","Aggregates"],"correct_options":["Aggregates"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank. After you configure the External signal activity in the destination workflow, the External signal activity will be available to configure in the ____________ activity of the source workflow.","presented_options":["Start","Jump","Wait","End"],"correct_options":["End"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  The source workflow must use the _______ activity to trigger a destination workflow.","presented_options":["Wait","Jump","End","Start"],"correct_options":["End"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which activity is used to trigger a workflow when some conditions are successfully met in another workflow or in a REST API call? ","presented_options":["Union","External signal","Scheduler","Wait"],"correct_options":["External signal"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which statement is true about the External signal activity?","presented_options":["The External signal activity is designed to be placed as the last activity of a workflow","You should first configure the External signal activity in the destination workflow","You can trigger an External signal activity from the Start activity of another workflow","You can organize processes that are part of different customer journeys into different workflows"],"correct_options":["You should first configure the External signal activity in the destination workflow"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statement is true about destination workflow?","presented_options":["You must start the destination workflow manually before it can be triggered","You must start the destination workflow for it to be available to select in the End activity of the source workflow","When you execute the End activity of the source workflow the destination workflow will be triggered"],"correct_options":["You must start the destination workflow manually before it can be triggered"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which statement is true about the External signal activity?","presented_options":["You should first configure the External signal activity in the source workflow","You can trigger an External signal activity from a SOAP API call","The external signal activity is designed to be placed as the first activity of the workflow","It allows you to start and stop a workflow from another workflow"],"correct_options":["The external signal activity is designed to be placed as the first activity of the workflow"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements is true about what you must do to link the source workflow with the destination workflow when configuring an external signal?","presented_options":["In the External signal of the destination workflow, select the source workflow","In the Start activity of the source workflow, select the destination workflow.","In the End activity of the source workflow, select the destination workflow","In the External signal of the source workflow, select the destination workflow"],"correct_options":["In the End activity of the source workflow, select the destination workflow"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Transactional messages can be sent to individuals who have opted out of email deliveries without violating the CAN-SPAM Act. True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When the corresponding event is modified, what happens to an existing event?","presented_options":["The existing event remains available only until the template is re-published","The existing event displays as unavailable until the template is re-published","The existing event changes based on the modifications","The existing event remains unchanged until the updated event is re-published"],"correct_options":["The existing event remains unchanged until the updated event is re-published"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are benefits of transactional messaging? ","presented_options":["Transactional messaging boosts overall performance of the Adobe Campaign platform","Transactional messaging enhances open and click-through rates compared to marketing messages","Transactional messaging adds new profiles to the DataMarrt for subsequent retargeting","Transactional messaging reduces IT costs through centralization","Transactional messsaging provides opportunities for additional sales by including limited marketing content","For known profiles, ability to enrich the transactional message with profile data"],"correct_options":["Transactional messaging enhances open and click-through rates compared to marketing messages","Transactional messaging reduces IT costs through centralization","Transactional messsaging provides opportunities for additional sales by including limited marketing content","For known profiles, ability to enrich the transactional message with profile data"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following stages are part of the lifecycle of a template? ","presented_options":["Published","Archived","Offline","Unpublished","Paused"],"correct_options":["Published","Unpublished","Paused"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following is the first step when configuring transactional messaging?","presented_options":["Integrate via API calls","Test and publish the template","Configure an event","Personalize the transactional message"],"correct_options":["Configure an event"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are characteristics of transactional messages? ","presented_options":["Highly promotional","Real-time or near real-time","Triggered","Scheduled"],"correct_options":["Real-time or near real-time","Triggered"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Transactional messages typically have a lower open rate than marketing messages. True or False?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When a template is paused, what happens to an incoming event?","presented_options":["The event is processed and the delivery is held for a future date and time","The event is discarded and an error message returned","The event is saved and processed later","The event is processed immediately"],"correct_options":["The event is saved and processed later"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How can Adobe's transactional messaging help reduce IT costs?","presented_options":["By permitting legacy systems to handle message sending","By allowing marketers to perform all IT tasks","By providing centralized system for sending notifications","By offering IT departments opportunities to gain proficiency at configuring marketing messages"],"correct_options":["By providing centralized system for sending notifications"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are examples of use cases for transactional messaging? Select the two correct answers.","presented_options":["New product launch notice","Order Confirmation","Discount sale offer","Password reset notification"],"correct_options":["Order Confirmation","Password reset notification"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following is the final step when configuring a transactional message?","presented_options":["Integrate via API calls","Test and publish the template","Configure an event","Personalize the transactional message"],"correct_options":["Integrate via API calls"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Standard: Technical Foundations for Business Practitioners ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If a profile has asked not to be contacted by any channel, where will this information be stored in ACS?","presented_options":["In the blacklist rules of the profile's attribues","In the blacklist rules of the channel attributes","In the Typology rules","In the Quarantines addresses"],"correct_options":["In the blacklist rules of the profile's attribues"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating Profiles and Audiences -TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which feature in ACS allows you to test personalization and dynamic content rendering in your email campaign?","presented_options":["Preview","Email Rendering","Trap"],"correct_options":["Preview"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating Profiles and Audiences -TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What does a profile correspond to in the Adobe Campaign Standard(ACS) database?","presented_options":["One contact stored in the Profiles table of the ACS database","One contact stored in either the profiles table or Test profiles table of the ACS database","One contact stored in the Audiences table of the ACS database","One contact stored in either the profiles table or Test profiles table, or the Audiences table of the ACS database"],"correct_options":["One contact stored in the Profiles table of the ACS database"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Creating Profiles and Audiences -TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You are working with an external agency to fulfill your direct mail campaign.  How will you determine whether your client list has been comprimized by the agency?","presented_options":["By using traps","By sending proofs","By using email rendering"],"correct_options":["By using traps"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Profiles and Audiences -TEST OUT","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"As best practice, Adobe Recommends the following hierarchy : ","presented_options":["Program > Sub-Programs > Campaigns > Workflows > Deliveries","Workflows > Deliveries > Program > Sub-Programs > Campaigns","Campaigns > Program > Sub-Programs > Workflows > Deliveries","Deliveries > Campaigns > Program > Sub-Programs > Workflows"],"correct_options":["Program > Sub-Programs > Campaigns > Workflows > Deliveries"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating Programs and  Campaigns - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are no longer contact black list options in a Campaign Standard Profile?","presented_options":["No longer contact (by any channel)","No longer contact by email","No longer contact by SMS","No longer contact by push notification","No longer contact by direct mail","No longer contact by facebook messenger","No longer contact by phone"],"correct_options":["No longer contact (by any channel)"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Programs and  Campaigns - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  Test profiles are _________ and ________________.","presented_options":["stored separately from profiles in the database","not included in delivery reports","stored in the same table with profiles in the database","included in delivery reports"],"correct_options":["stored separately from profiles in the database","not included in delivery reports"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Programs and  Campaigns - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which email type is only available within a workflow and is can be sent multiple times to different targets over a defined period?","presented_options":["Recurring email","Single-send email","A/B test email","Transactional message"],"correct_options":["Recurring email"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Creating an Email Delivery - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of email is set once to a defined target.","presented_options":["Single-send email","Recurring email","A/B test email","Transactional message"],"correct_options":["Single-send email"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating an Email Delivery - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which type of email is used to setup three versions of an email?","presented_options":["Single-send email","Recurring email","A/B test email","Transactional message"],"correct_options":["A/B test email"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating an Email Delivery - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which email type is for individual and unique email sent once to a customer, triggerd by that customer's behavior?","presented_options":["Single-send email","Recurring email","A/B test email","Transactional message"],"correct_options":["Transactional message"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating an Email Delivery - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are the proper sequence of steps when creating an email delivery?","presented_options":["Select Type->Set Properties->Specify Audience->Design Content->Prepare & Send","Design Content->Select Type->Set Properties->Specify Audience->Prepare & Send","Select Type->Design Content->Specify Audience->Set Properties->Prepare & Send","Design Content->Specify Audience->Select Type->Set Properties->Prepare & Send"],"correct_options":["Select Type->Set Properties->Specify Audience->Design Content->Prepare & Send"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Designing Content with the Email Designer - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When selecting an email to allow messages to be sent automatically on the date specified below, what are the Optimize settings you can select?","presented_options":["No optimization","Send at the recipient's time zone","Send at a custom date defined by a formula","Send at the Adobe Campain Data Center Time zone","Send Immediately"],"correct_options":["No optimization","Send at the recipient's time zone","Send at a custom date defined by a formula"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Designing Content with the Email Designer - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In the Email Designer for a content fragment, what are the  Content Type options that are available?","presented_options":["Shared","Delivery","Landing Page","SMS","Text Only"],"correct_options":["Shared","Delivery","Landing Page"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Creating a Content Fragment - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In the Email Designer for a content fragment, what are the  HTML Type options that are available?","presented_options":["Fragment","Template","HTML & CSS","HTML5 & CSS","Text Only"],"correct_options":["Fragment","Template"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Creating a Content Fragment - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If an email contains dynamic content, and some profies can meet mulitple conditions, how can a business practitioner ensure that a specific piece of content is guaranteed to be shown?","presented_options":["BP would set the priority for the each condition to have the highest priority","BP would set the priority for the each condition to have the lowest priority","BP would set the priority for the each condition to have the priority set to '<MAX>'","The BP is unable to set priority as Dynamic Content uses A.I. algorithm to select the best content for an audience."],"correct_options":["BP would set the priority for the each condition to have the highest priority"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Personalizing Email Content - custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"As a BP, how can you validate personalized content is correct for a particular email before sending to the targeted audience without impacting reporting?","presented_options":["Preview design using Desktop View & Responsive Mobile View","Use a test profile to test personalization and dynamic content","Use a standard profile to test personalization and dynamic content","Preview the screen shot of the rendered email that is saved within the Campaign Activity"],"correct_options":["Preview design using Desktop View & Responsive Mobile View","Use a test profile to test personalization and dynamic content"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Personalizing Email Content - custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When preparing a delivery, what are the types of Typology Rules?","presented_options":["Filtering rules","Control rules","Fatigue management rules","Black list rules","Spam blocking rules","Accessibility rules"],"correct_options":["Filtering rules","Control rules","Fatigue management rules"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"True or False,  In order to create an A/B Test you must select an email with a template that matches the type of test you want to conduct.  ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Templates are provided and support the following types of A/B tests: ","presented_options":["A/B test on sender","A/B test on content","A/B test on subject","A/B test on SMS vs Email","A/B test on recipient","A/B test on Push notification","A/B test on In-App message"],"correct_options":["A/B test on sender","A/B test on content","A/B test on subject"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When setting up an A/B test, you can choose how many variants?","presented_options":["only 2","two or three","up to 5","unlimited"],"correct_options":["two or three"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When setting up an A/B test, you can choose the following winning strategies?","presented_options":["Best open rate","Best click-through rate","Weakest unsubscription rate","Max revenue","Best conversion rate"],"correct_options":["Best open rate","Best click-through rate","Weakest unsubscription rate"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When setting up an A/B test, if you select to test 3 A/B/C variants, you can switch to 2 variants at a later time if desired.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When setting up an A/B Test, if you manually assign a percentage for the target audience to one variant the other variant(s) will be forced to receive the same percentage?","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When setting up an A/B Test and manually assigning the percentage of target audience to each variant, the remaining percentage of traffic will receive ________ variant?","presented_options":["the winning","a round-robin","a random","the control group","the hold out group"],"correct_options":["the winning"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The minimum A/B test duration can be set to is?","presented_options":["1 hour","1 day","1 week","2 weeks","3 days"],"correct_options":["1 hour"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In an A/B Test, which Winner sending method requires you to manually select the winning variant?","presented_options":["Send after confirmation","Send Automatically","Send after 24 hours","Send after 1 hour"],"correct_options":["Send after confirmation"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In an A/B test, what are some reasons a BP would want to select the winning variant manually?","presented_options":["If you choose to manually confirm the winner","If you choose to manually confirm the winner in the case of a tie","At any time to reduce the test duration","To override the winning variant"],"correct_options":["If you choose to manually confirm the winner in the case of a tie","At any time to reduce the test duration"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Sending an Email - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true regarding content components in Adobe Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Content components can be displayed across mulitple columns of a structure component","Carousel, social and divider are content components available in ACS","Content components are empty components","Content components cannot be inserted into structure components"],"correct_options":["Carousel, social and divider are content components available in ACS","Content components are empty components"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What do the programs and campaigns in Adobe Campaign Standard let you do?","presented_options":["Regroup all the different marketing activities linked to a campaign","Plan and organize marketing campaigns","Generate reports on programs and camapaigns","Transfer files within campaigns","Reuse marketing activities within the same campaign or program"],"correct_options":["Regroup all the different marketing activities linked to a campaign","Generate reports on programs and camapaigns","Plan and organize marketing campaigns"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following components can you use to insert the content into your email design?","presented_options":["Content Components","Structure Components","Content Fragments","Video Components","JavaScript Components"],"correct_options":["Content Components","Structure Components","Content Fragments"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which element can be edited separately for mobile display?","presented_options":["Text","Images","Font size","Structure of the email content"],"correct_options":["Font size"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Tracking results are avaialable in the tracking logs of a delivery that has been sent.  Which reports are available out of the box for reviewing the results?","presented_options":["Delivery Summary","Tracking Indicators","Hot Clicks","URLs and Click Streams","Report Summary","Subscription Summary"],"correct_options":["Delivery Summary","Tracking Indicators","Hot Clicks","URLs and Click Streams"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When checking the send status for both Direct Mail and Email, what tabs are available to both types when reviewing log files?","presented_options":["LOG","SENDING LOGS","EXCLUSION LOGS","EXCLUSION CAUSES","TRACKING LOGS","TRACKED URLS"],"correct_options":["LOG","SENDING LOGS","EXCLUSION LOGS","EXCLUSION CAUSES"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When selecting the Explore file option for a direct mail campaign, the ____ are displayed in the preview.","presented_options":["first 10 lines","first 25 lines","first 1000 lines","entire file contents","first 100 lines"],"correct_options":["first 100 lines"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Create and Send email Campaigns - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What do you need to do if you change the audience of a direct mail delivery after preparing it for delivery?","presented_options":["Prepare the delivery again","Explore the file","Regnerate the file","Confirm the delivery","Refresh the page","Exit the Email and re-enter"],"correct_options":["Prepare the delivery again"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ACS Channels  - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which channels in ACS support multilingual campaigns?","presented_options":["Push notifications","SMS","Email","In-App messaging","Direct mail","Voice mail"],"correct_options":["Push notifications","SMS","Email"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Channels  - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the out of the box templates provided for creating landing pages?","presented_options":["Profile acquisition","Blacklist (global)","Subscription","Unsubscription","Product Detail Page","Pre-Release Sign up Page","Whitelist {global)"],"correct_options":["Profile acquisition","Blacklist (global)","Subscription","Unsubscription"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Creating Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When setting up the properties for a Subscription landing page, what are the profile options available in the Acess & Loading Section for Targeting dimension Profiles(profile) section?","presented_options":["Authorize visitor identification via URL parameters","Preload visitor data","Authorize unidentified visitors","Require unidentfied visitors to sign in","Redirect to error page for unidentified visitors"],"correct_options":["Authorize unidentified visitors","Preload visitor data","Authorize visitor identification via URL parameters"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Creating Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When setting up the properties for a landing page, if you want to send a confirmation message on subscription, what type of message template would you need to select for the email?","presented_options":["Transactional","Welcome","Default","Any","Subscription Confirmation"],"correct_options":["Transactional"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Creating Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When setting up the properties for a UnSubscription landing page, what are the profile options available in the Acess & Loading Section for Targeting dimension Profiles(profile) section?","presented_options":["Use reCAPTCHA to protect your site from spam and abuse","Authorize visitor identification via URL Parameters","Preload visitor data","Authorize unidentified visitors","Redirect to error page for unidentified visitors"],"correct_options":["Preload visitor data","Authorize visitor identification via URL Parameters","Use reCAPTCHA to protect your site from spam and abuse"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Creating Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When setting up a landing page, Links can have their Target property set to which options?","presented_options":["Default browser behavior","Current window(_self)","New window(_blank)","Parent window(_parent)","Top window(_top)","Other(iFrame)","Pop-Up window(_popup)"],"correct_options":["Default browser behavior","Current window(_self)","New window(_blank)","Parent window(_parent)","Top window(_top)","Other(iFrame)"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Creating Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"How is a profile subscribed to a service?","presented_options":["The profile subscribes itself to a service using the services subscription link","Profiles are subscribed to a service via the Subscription services activity in a workflow","Profiles are subscribed to a service by clicking Add and selecting the profile in the service properties","Profiles are subscribed to a service using the Save Audience activity in a workflow"],"correct_options":["The profile subscribes itself to a service using the services subscription link","Profiles are subscribed to a service via the Subscription services activity in a workflow"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"ACS Create and Publish Services and Landing pages - Test out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which UI element contains all the activities in Campaign Standard?","presented_options":["Pallette","Workspace","Quick Actions","Actions Bar"],"correct_options":["Pallette"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Create Workflows - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following statements are true about the out-of-the-box technical workflows in ACS?","presented_options":["They leverage the tracking information in deliveries","They do not update provisional jobs on deliveries","They carry out maintenance operations on audience profiles","Their jobs must be executed once a month on the server"],"correct_options":["They leverage the tracking information in deliveries"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Create Workflows - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"How are workflows used in Adobe Campain Standard?","presented_options":["To export data from the database","To manage technical processes, such ase database cleanup and recovering tracking informaiton","To customize data","To create 360-degree audience profiles","To design an email content for email delivery"],"correct_options":["To export data from the database","To manage technical processes, such ase database cleanup and recovering tracking informaiton","To customize data"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Create Workflows - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  To automate tasks, such as preparing data for targeting, personalization, and reporting in Campaign Standard, we use a __________.","presented_options":["Workflow","Segment","Data Structure","Workspace","Campaign"],"correct_options":["Workflow"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Create Workflows - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In a workflow, what does the Data Structure Tab in the properties of the transition display?","presented_options":["Worktable schema","Communication channels","Workflow activitiies","Worktable records"],"correct_options":["Worktable schema"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Create Workflows - Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are limit options for the size of a segment?","presented_options":["Segment code","Minimum size","Size(as a % of the initial population)","Maximum size"],"correct_options":["Size(as a % of the initial population)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Segment Data using Workflows- Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which of the following segmentation activity properties will result in concurrent workflow paths for each segment?","presented_options":["Generate one transition per segment","Enable overlapping of outbound populations","Generaate the complement","Generate all segments in the same transition"],"correct_options":["Generate one transition per segment"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Segment Data using Workflows- Test Out","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In the extraction tab for Extract File activity, what are the post-processing stage options?","presented_options":["None","Zip","Convert to TSV","Convert to Pipe(|) delimited"],"correct_options":["None","Zip"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations - Exporting Data Using a Workflow - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In the Extract file Export Activity, if you did not want repetitive rows of data returned in the file which option would you select?","presented_options":["Group by","Unqiue values only","Ignore duplicates","Remove duplicate rows(DISTINCT)"],"correct_options":["Remove duplicate rows(DISTINCT)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations - Exporting Data Using a Workflow-Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In the Extract File Export activity, what column separators are available by using either CSV or Text for the output format?","presented_options":["Comma","Tabulation","Semicolon","Other ( & user selects separator in text field)","Hashtag( #)","Fixed Width(& user specifies column widths)"],"correct_options":["Comma","Tabulation","Semicolon","Other ( & user selects separator in text field)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations - Exporting Data Using a Workflow-Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When Creating an import template, if you need to upload a new version of a sample file, what option would you select to do so?","presented_options":["Drop a new sample file","Overwrite existing","Re-upload sample file","Re-import"],"correct_options":["Drop a new sample file"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations - Creating an import template - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In the save Audience workflow Activity, what are the available options to save an audience?","presented_options":["Update an existing audience","Create or update an audience","Create a unique audience","Share in Adobe Experience Cloud","Remove an audience","Creat a test audience","Remove a test audience"],"correct_options":["Update an existing audience","Create or update an audience","Create a unique audience","Share in Adobe Experience Cloud"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations - Creating an import template - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In the Update Data workflow Activity, what are the valid Operation type options?","presented_options":["Insert or update","Insert only","Update","Delete","Remove duplicates","Insert Distinct","Set In-active"],"correct_options":["Insert or update","Insert only","Update","Delete"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations - Creating an import template - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  _______ are Messages sent in real-time or near real-time, triggered, and notification type deliveries.","presented_options":["Transactional messages","Push Notifications","In-App Messages","Emails"],"correct_options":["Transactional messages"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Ovrview of transactional Messaging","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What are the proper sequence of steps to configure transactional messaging?","presented_options":["Configure an event -> Personalize the transactional message -> Test and publish the template -> Integrate via API Calls","Configure an event ->  Integrate via API Calls -> Personalize the transactional message -> Test and publish the template","Configure an event -> Personalize the transactional message -> Integrate via API Calls -> Test and publish the template","Integrate via API Calls - > Configure an event -> Personalize the transactional message -> Test and publish the template"],"correct_options":["Configure an event -> Personalize the transactional message -> Test and publish the template -> Integrate via API Calls"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Transactional Messages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"During the template lifecycle and event processing, when an template is in a Paused state what happens to incoming REST API events?","presented_options":["Incoming events are queued","Incoming events are  processed and messages sent","Incoming events are not processed"],"correct_options":["Incoming events are queued"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"During the template lifecycle and event processing, when an template is in a Draft state what happens to incoming REST API events?","presented_options":["Incoming events are queued","Incoming events are  processed and messages sent","Incoming events are not processed"],"correct_options":["Incoming events are not processed"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"During the template lifecycle and event processing, when an template is Published state what happens to incoming REST API events?","presented_options":["Incoming events are queued","Incoming events are  processed and messages sent","Incoming events are not processed"],"correct_options":["Incoming events are  processed and messages sent"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"After unpublishing template, how long will you have to wait before publishing the template again in order for ACS to clean up the event queue?","presented_options":["24 hrs","1 hr","10 days","1 week"],"correct_options":["24 hrs"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In order to rollout an event API, what steps must occur?","presented_options":["Publish the event","Configure the template","Publish the template","Manually create the REST API","Publish the REST API"],"correct_options":["Publish the event","Configure the template","Publish the template"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"If you want to modify the exsiting event API call parameters, what steps must you take before performing the rollout api steps?","presented_options":["Unpublish the template","Modify the event","Pause the REST API","Unpublish the Rest API","Modify the RESPT API Parameters"],"correct_options":["Unpublish the template","Modify the event"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you wish to temporarily buffer transactional messages requests, what steps should you take?","presented_options":["Pause the template -> When ready resume the template","Unpublish the template -> When ready re-publish the template","Stop the REST API Service - > when ready re-start the REST API Service"],"correct_options":["Pause the template -> When ready resume the template"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Technical Foundations: Managing Transactional Templates","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"In addition to the number of messages to send and those successfully processed, what information is availlable in the default Transactional delivery summary Report?","presented_options":["Bounces","Quarantines","Clicks","Click Through Rate","Open Rate","Unique Clicks"],"correct_options":["Bounces","Quarantines"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Reporting and Monitoring : Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where do you go to set the warning and alert levels on a report?","presented_options":["Adminstration - > Application Settings -> Options","Application -> Control Panel -> Options","Administration -> Instance Settings -> Options","Administration-> Deployment -> Options","Resources -> Templates -> Service templates -> Options"],"correct_options":["Adminstration - > Application Settings -> Options"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Reporting and Monitoring : Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The following steps used to assist in Troubleshooting what?Once published, a batch job is created to handle publication.  You can see results by clicking on previous publication's tab inside event configuration.  Click on publication - you can see associated batch job as well as the error.","presented_options":["troubleshoot publishing an event","troubleshoot publishing a Template","troubleshoot API Calls","troubleshoot message execution"],"correct_options":["troubleshoot publishing an event"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Transactional Messages Troubleshooting: ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The following steps used to assist in Troubleshooting what?  Go to log section to view the information about when template was published.  You can download this log to .csv file for further analysis.","presented_options":["troubleshoot publishing an event","troubleshoot publishing a Template","troubleshoot API Calls","troubleshoot message execution"],"correct_options":["troubleshoot publishing a Template"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Transactional Messages Troubleshooting: ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The following steps used to assist in Troubleshooting what?  Use a get request to query the event status(append the history ID to the vent Request URL).","presented_options":["troubleshoot publishing an event","troubleshoot publishing a Template","troubleshoot API Calls","troubleshoot message execution"],"correct_options":["troubleshoot API Calls"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Transactional Messages Troubleshooting: ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The following steps used to assist in Troubleshooting what?   Go to Transaction template -> execution list.  One delvery is created for each time you publish the template.  Open that delivery and view any errors in the logs.","presented_options":["troubleshoot publishing an event","troubleshoot publishing a Template","troubleshoot API Calls","troubleshoot message execution"],"correct_options":["troubleshoot message execution"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Transactional Messages Troubleshooting: ","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of message provides a second chance to reach the recipient with important information.  These messages are sent via the same channel, have same targeting dimension and generate event dleivery and tracking logs, or profile delivery and tracking logs.","presented_options":["Follow-up Messages","Push Notifications","In-App Messages"],"correct_options":["Follow-up Messages"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Design and Management: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How would a BP generate a follow-up message template?","presented_options":["Activate the checkbox in the Template configuration & Add Subject line and body","Create a Follow up Template","Activate the Follow-up event in the event workflow","Activate the checkbox in the event configuration & Add Subject line and body"],"correct_options":["Activate the checkbox in the event configuration & Add Subject line and body"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Design and Management: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How would a BP identify recipients that should receive a follow-up message?","presented_options":["Identify recipients of the transaction message by comparing that the recipient delivery log exists and the recipient's tracking log does not exist","Identify recipients of the transaction message by comparing that the recipient delivery log does not exist and the recipient's tracking log does not exist","Identify recipients of the transaction message by comparing that the recipient delivery log does not exist and the recipient's tracking log exists","Identify recipients of the transaction message by comparing that the recipient delivery log exists and the recipient's tracking log exists"],"correct_options":["Identify recipients of the transaction message by comparing that the recipient delivery log exists and the recipient's tracking log does not exist"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Design and Management: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  _________ are part of the Activation Core Service and are used to send transactional messages when certain conditions are met.","presented_options":["Adobe Marketing Cloud Triggers","Activation Messages","Marketing Cloud Messages","Marketing Cloud Events"],"correct_options":["Adobe Marketing Cloud Triggers"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Design and Management: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where would a BP go to setup Adobe Marketing Cloud Triggers?","presented_options":["Marketing Plans -> Transactional Messages -> Maketing Cloud triggers","Administration -> WorkFlow -> Maketing Cloud triggers","Administration -> Transactional Messages -> Maketing Cloud triggers"],"correct_options":["Marketing Plans -> Transactional Messages -> Maketing Cloud triggers"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Design and Management: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"How should a BP filter out users that are likely to come back to the site on their own without receiving a transactional message form a Marketing cloud trigger?","presented_options":["In the Marketing cloud trigger configuration, select the filter users likely to return","In the Marketing cloud trigger configuration, Target the audience profile that matches  \"likely to return\""],"correct_options":["In the Marketing cloud trigger configuration, Target the audience profile that matches  \"likely to return\""],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Campaign Design and Management: Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You are setting up an email campaign for an upcoming event.  The business team you are working with needs to proofread the contents of the delivery before it is sent out to your audience.  How would you ensure that the business team receives proofs?","presented_options":["Create your own test profile, send a proof test message to yourself, and forward the message to the business team.","Create an email rendering test profile for each business team member and send a proof test message.","Create a proof test profile for each business team member and send a proof test message.","Create a proof test profile for each business team member and send an email rendering test message."],"correct_options":["Create a proof test profile for each business team member and send a proof test message."],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which three elements can be duplicated, modified and resused.","presented_options":["Campaigns","Test Profiles","Field Names","Workflows","Query Activity","Segmentation Activity"],"correct_options":["Campaigns","Workflows","Test Profiles"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Following Campaign Standard default control rules, what should always be included in the body copy of an email delivery?","presented_options":["Subject line","Personalized greetings","Preheader","Unsubscribe link"],"correct_options":["Unsubscribe link"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In each email, you want the customer's first name to appear first in the subject line.   What steps need to happen so the customer's first name appears first in the subject line?","presented_options":["Click on the Edit button of the subject line.     Click Insert Personalization Field.     Insert the first name field from the profile    Finish writing the subject line.   Click Save","Click on the Edit button of the subject line       Enable dynamic text      Insert the first name field from the profile       Finish writing the subject line     Click Save","Click on the Edit button of the subject line.      Insert a Content Block    Insert the first name field from the profile     Finish writing the subject line.     Click Save","Click on the Edit button of the subject line     Right Click to bring up personalization options    Insert the first name field from the Profile      Finish writing the subject line       Click Save"],"correct_options":["Click on the Edit button of the subject line.     Click Insert Personalization Field.     Insert the first name field from the profile    Finish writing the subject line.   Click Save"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What does fatigue rule exclude?","presented_options":["over-solicited profiles","quarantied addresses","blacklisted addresses","over-sized messages"],"correct_options":["over-solicited profiles"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"After sending an email delivery, a few of the targeted profiles did not receive the email.  Where should be the first place you check to investigate this error?","presented_options":["In the Deployment summary select the ellipsis icon(…), then go to Log and Tracking Logs","In the Deployment summary select the ellipsis icon(…), then go to Log and Exclusion Logs","In the Deployment summary select the ellipsis icon(…), then go to Log and Sending Logs"],"correct_options":["In the Deployment summary select the ellipsis icon(…), then go to Log and Exclusion Logs"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You have just deployed an email campaign and need to review the message logs.  Where do you find the message logs?","presented_options":["Select the report icon in the action bar","Select the elipsis inon (…) in the confiugration panel","Select the Reports link in the top navigation","Select the elipsis icon (…) at the bottom right of the deployment summary"],"correct_options":["Select the elipsis icon (…) at the bottom right of the deployment summary"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What is the reason for the delivery failure type, 'User unknown'","presented_options":["The email address does not exist","The email address was placed in quarantine","The email address is not defined","The email address was blacklisted at the time of sending"],"correct_options":["The email address does not exist"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which are the types of errors when a delivery fails?","presented_options":["Hard, Soft, Ignored and Duplicate","Hard and Soft Errors","Bounce","Hard, Soft, and Ignored"],"correct_options":["Hard, Soft, and Ignored"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"After sending an email delivery, you were asked to provide feedback on the email performance.  What information can you provide from the delivery deployment dashboard? ","presented_options":["The percentage of messages opened","The percentage of messages that were forwarded by recipients","The percentage of messages that were viewed in text format","The percentage of clicks in the message","The percentage of messages that were marked as spam by recipients"],"correct_options":["The percentage of messages opened","The percentage of clicks in the message"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You would like to split the target audience into three groups based on different profile attributes.  Which workflow activity would you use?","presented_options":["Incremental query","Fork","Segmentation","Enrichment"],"correct_options":["Segmentation"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which workflow activity can be used to remove the results of a Subscription Services activity from the final target?","presented_options":["Deduplication","Exclusion","Query","Intersection"],"correct_options":["Exclusion"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A business team would like to send out an automated email to their subscribers on their birthday.  What workflow activities would you need to include?","presented_options":["Scheduler, Segmentation, Email","Read Audience, Segmentation, Email","Incremental Query, Read Audience, Email","Scheduler, Query, Email"],"correct_options":["Scheduler, Query, Email"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"A marketer wants to create an Audience from the subscribers of a particular newsletter service.  How would you create a new list audience of subscribers in a workflow?","presented_options":["Adminstration - > Application Settings -> Workflows > Create a workflow        Add a Save Audience Activity          Create an audience","Administration > Application Settings > Workflows > Create a workflow       Add a Query to filter the subscribers     Add a Save audience activity","Marketing Activities > Create a workflow        Add a Query to filter the subscribers       Add a Save audience Activity","Profiles and Audiences > Audiences      Create an audience     Add a Query to filter the subscribers"],"correct_options":["Marketing Activities > Create a workflow        Add a Query to filter the subscribers       Add a Save audience Activity"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"You received a request for a plan to send several campaigns to a specific target of profiles.   Knowing that the database of profiles is updated regularly for new profiles, modified ones, or expired addresses, what type of Audience would you crate so that the audience data is automatically recomputed in every future use?","presented_options":["List Audience","Query Audience","File Audience","Experience Cloud Audience"],"correct_options":["Query Audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"What out-of-the-box content block should be added to the email content to allow the recipient to view the email content in a browser?","presented_options":["Add a custom content block","Link to a landing page created in Adobe Campaign","Linnk to the brand website","Link to a mirror page"],"correct_options":["Link to a mirror page"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"ADO-E302 Campaign Standard BP Sample test","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of workflow targeting activity allows you to filter and extract a population of elements from the Adobe Campaign Database.  Each time this activity is executed, the results from the previous executions are excluded, which allows you to target only new elements. ","presented_options":["Incremental Query","Query","Segmentation","Read Audience","Intersection","Exclusion"],"correct_options":["Incremental Query"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"An Incremental Query has to be linked to a Scheduler in order to define the execution frequency of the workflow and therefore the query. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When performing an incremental query, which tab allows you to view any results of the activity's previous executions?","presented_options":["Processed data","Delivery Logs","Transaction Logs","Data Archive"],"correct_options":["Processed data"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When defining additional data for Incremental query workflows, the data is stored in additional columns and can ONLY be used for the workflow in progress. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which workflow targeting  Activity is the best choice if you want to regroup the result of multiple activities into a single target?","presented_options":["Union","Query","Incrmental Query","Enrichment","Deduplication"],"correct_options":["Union"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of workflow targeting  activity is often used to combine the populations form inbound transitions when performing a segmentation, defining an audience or when preparing a message target.","presented_options":["Union","Query","Incrmental Query","Enrichment","Deduplication"],"correct_options":["Union"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When setting up a Union Workflow targeting  activity, if you want  to control how the inbound population data is handled, you can choose which Reconcilliation Types?","presented_options":["Keys only","All shared columns","A selection of columns","# of Initial Column(s)","All disparate columns","All Empty Columns(null)"],"correct_options":["Keys only","All shared columns","A selection of columns"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which workflow targeting  Activity allows you to keep only the elements common to the different inbound populations in the activity?","presented_options":["Intersection","Incremtnal Query","Union","Enrichment","Deduplication"],"correct_options":["Intersection"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which workflow targeting  activty allows you to exclude elements form one population according to certain criteria?","presented_options":["Exclusion","Deduplication","Union","Read Audience","Intersection"],"correct_options":["Exclusion"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Which workflow targeting  activity lets you create one or several segments from a population calculated by activities placed earlier in the workflow. At the end of the activity, they can be processed in one single transition or different transitions.","presented_options":["Segmentation","Enrichment","Union","Incremental Query","Save Audience","Intersection"],"correct_options":["Segmentation"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The targeting  workflow Segmentation activity is generally placed before targeting activities (query, intersection, union, exclusion, etc.) in order to define the standard population based on which the segments are formed.","presented_options":["False","True"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When setting up a Segmentation workflow targeting Activity, the following types of outbound transitions are available for selection:","presented_options":["Generate one transition per segment","Generate all segments in one transition","Generate transitions for new segments","Generate transitions for exclusion segments"],"correct_options":["Generate one transition per segment","Generate all segments in one transition"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When using the segmentation workflow targeting  activity, this option allows you exclude the specified segment from the outbound population of the activity. This option can only be used if the 'Generate all Segments in the same tranisiton' is used. ","presented_options":["Exclude segment from population","Omit segment","Dedup Segment","Block Segment form population"],"correct_options":["Exclude segment from population"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When using the segmentaiton workflow targeting  activity, if you wanted to limit the output population, what are the 'Types of Limit' options you can select for how the sample is chosen?","presented_options":["Random Sampling","Ordered Sampling","Odd & Even Sampling","First N Sampling","Uniques Sampling"],"correct_options":["Random Sampling","Ordered Sampling"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When using the segmentation workflow targeting activity, the following options are avaiable to Limit the size of the segment.","presented_options":["Size (as a % of the initial population)","Maximum size","By data grouping","By data grouping (as a %)","Minimum and Maximum size"],"correct_options":["Size (as a % of the initial population)","Maximum size","By data grouping","By data grouping (as a %)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This type of workflow targeting activity is best used if you want to retrieve an existing audience and refine it by applying additional filtering conditions.","presented_options":["Read Audience","Incremental Query","Query","Intersection","Segmentation"],"correct_options":["Read Audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This targeting workflow activity is a simpler version of the Query activity and is designed for cases where you only need to select an existing audience.","presented_options":["Read Audience","Incremental Query","Query","Intersection","Segmentation"],"correct_options":["Read Audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This targeting workflow activity allows you to update an existing audience or create a new audience from the population computed upstream in a workflow. The audiences created or updated from this activity are List or File audiences. They are added to the list of application audiences, and are made available via the Audiences menu.","presented_options":["Save audience","Read Audience","Intersection","Segmentation","Incremental Query"],"correct_options":["Save audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow targeting activity allows you to export profiles as Adobe Experience Cloud audiences/segments. This then allows you to exploit these audiences in other Adobe Experience Cloud solutions.","presented_options":["Save audience","Read Audience","Intersection","Segmentation","Incremental Query"],"correct_options":["Save audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When selecting the action for the Save audience workflow targeting activity, the following options are available for ways one can 'Update an existing Audience'.","presented_options":["Replace audience content with new data : The whole of the audience content is replaced.","Complete audience with new data : The old audience data is kept and the data from the save audience activity's inbound transition is added to it.","Update only modified Data.  Only field values that have changed are updated","Update new values by date : Only records modified since the selected date are added/updated."],"correct_options":["Replace audience content with new data : The whole of the audience content is replaced.","Complete audience with new data : The old audience data is kept and the data from the save audience activity's inbound transition is added to it."],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When performing a Save audience workflow target activity, If the targeting dimension of the audience is unknown when it is saved (for example if it is from an imported file), the audience is created or updated as a ____  type audience.","presented_options":["File","List","ACS Audience Only","Unverified"],"correct_options":["File"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When performing a Save audience workflow target activity, If the targeting dimension of the saved audience is already defined when it is saved (for example, if it comes from a targeting, after a query, etc.), then the audience is saved or updated as a _____  type of audience.","presented_options":["List Audience","File","ACS Audience Only","Verified","Experience Cloud Audience"],"correct_options":["List Audience"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Within the Deduplicaiton workflow target activity, a value of '0' for the Number of Unique Records to keep, will remove all Duplicates.  ","presented_options":["False","True"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Within the Deduplicaiton workflow target activity, a value of '0' for the Number of Unique Records to keep, will Keep all Duplicates.  ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Which of the following are options for Deduplicliation Method?","presented_options":["Choose for me - randomly selects the record to be kept out of the duplicates","Following a list of values : lets you define a value priority for one or more fields","Non-empty value : this lets you keep records for which the value of the selected expression is not empty as a priority","Using an expression : this lets you keep the records in which the value of the expression entered is the smallest or the biggest.","Auto-Removal - based on AI algorithm in ACS Expeiernce Cloud"],"correct_options":["Choose for me - randomly selects the record to be kept out of the duplicates","Following a list of values : lets you define a value priority for one or more fields","Non-empty value : this lets you keep records for which the value of the selected expression is not empty as a priority","Using an expression : this lets you keep the records in which the value of the expression entered is the smallest or the biggest."],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow targeting activity is an advanced activity that allows you to define additional data to process in your workflow.","presented_options":["Enrichment","Query","Intersection","Deduplicaiton","Incremental Query"],"correct_options":["Enrichment"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"With this type of workflow targeting activity you can leverage the inbound transition and configure the activity to complete the output transition with additional data. It allows to combine data coming from multiple sets, or to create links to a temporary resource.","presented_options":["Enrichment","Query","Intersection","Deduplicaiton","Incremental Query"],"correct_options":["Enrichment"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This grouping of workflow activities are specific to organizing and executing workflows. Their main task is to coordinate the other activities.","presented_options":["Execution activities","Targeting activities","Channel activities","Data management activities"],"correct_options":["Execution activities"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  It is a best practice to use a(n) ____ activity instead of leaving the last transition of a workflow on its own to ensure that the workflow properly ends.","presented_options":["End","Start","Deduplication","Close","Stop","Exit"],"correct_options":["End"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can configure the Executing workflow Activity End to Stop all tasks in progress and once the corresponding task has finished it will have the same effect as if the Stop button had been selected.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"SIngle Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  You can trigger another workflow by configuring the ____ tab of an End Workflow Exceuting Activity.","presented_options":["External signal","External Process","Outbound Process","Trigger Event"],"correct_options":["External signal"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This Workflow Executing activity allows you to create outbound transitions to start several activities as the same time.","presented_options":["Fork","Union","And-Join","Scheduler","External Signal"],"correct_options":["Fork"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow Executing activity allows you to synchronize muliple execution branches of a workflow.","presented_options":["AND-Join","Fork","Union","Scheduler","Trigger Event"],"correct_options":["AND-Join"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow Executing activity allows you to determine when a workflow or an activity is Started.","presented_options":["Scheduler","Incrmental Query","Test","Fork","Start and end"],"correct_options":["Scheduler"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"The following are all options for specifying when a Workflow Execution Scheduler activity will expire: ","presented_options":["Never","After a certain number of iterations","On a specific date","Tomorrow","Upon first completion"],"correct_options":["Never","After a certain number of iterations","On a specific date"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow executing activity  momentarily suspends executing a part of a workflow. It activates its outbound transition after a delay that may range from a few seconds to several months, which executes the activities placed afterwards.","presented_options":["Wait","Scheduler","Union","Fork","And-Join","Pause","Delay"],"correct_options":["Wait"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow executing activity triggers a workflow when some conditions are succesfully met in another workflow or from a REST API call.","presented_options":["External signal","Outbound process","Trigger Event","REST API"],"correct_options":["External signal"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The workflow executing activity is designed to be placed as the first activity of a workflow. It can be triggered from the End activity of another workflow or from a REST API call (for more on this, refer to the API documentation ).","presented_options":["Outbound Process","Trigger Evetnt","External signal","REST API","Start"],"correct_options":["External signal"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"When configuring an external signal, it is important to first configure the External signal activity in the destination workflow. Once this configuration is done, the External signal activity of this workflow becomes available to configure the End activity of the source workflow.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow executing activity enables a transition based on a test result.","presented_options":["Test","Query","Incrmental Query","And-Join","Intersection"],"correct_options":["Test"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This workflow executing activity activates the first transition that satisfies the condition associated to it.","presented_options":["Test","Query","Incrmental Query","And-Join","Intersection"],"correct_options":["Test"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"You can combine workflow channel activities, within a single workflow to create a cross-channel workflow.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you want to setup a recurring email, you will need to link the email Delivery activity with what other Execution activity?","presented_options":["Scheduler","External signal","Wait","Save Audience"],"correct_options":["Scheduler"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  As a BP, if you wanted to send out a Birthday email daily, but receive reports on your delivery on a monthly basis.  You would need to set the aggregate sends per  ________","presented_options":["Month","Day","Calendar Date","Bi-Monthly"],"correct_options":["Month"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When setting up an Email Delivery Channel workflow activity, if you wanted to generate an outbound transition that contains the Exact same population as the inbound transition , you need to select ___________ .","presented_options":["Add outbound transition without the population","Add outbound transition with the population"],"correct_options":["Add outbound transition without the population"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When setting up an Email Delivery Channel workflow activity, if you wanted to generate an outbound transition containing the population to whom the email was sent. The members of the target excluded during the delivery preparation (quarantine, invalid email, etc.) are excluded from this transition , you need to select ___________  .","presented_options":["Add outbound transition without the population","Add outbound transition with the population"],"correct_options":["Add outbound transition with the population"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  The deliveries created within a channel activity workflow can be accessed from ___________________","presented_options":["the application's marketing activity list","Workflow Logs","Delivery Send Notification Logs","Workflow Reporting Section"],"correct_options":["the application's marketing activity list"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  As a BP, if you wanted to tartget people who where sent an email, but did not open the email.  You can utilize a query that includes a check that a record   ________  and  _________","presented_options":["exists in Delivery logs(logs)     &     does not exist in Tracking Logs(logs)","does not exist in Delivery logs(logs)     &     does not exist in Tracking Logs(logs)","exists in Delivery logs(logs)     &     exists in Tracking Logs(logs)","does not exist in Delivery logs(logs)     &     exists in Tracking Logs(logs)"],"correct_options":["exists in Delivery logs(logs)     &     does not exist in Tracking Logs(logs)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  The executions of recurring deliveries for channel activities are masked by default. To view them, check the ________________ option in the marketing activities' search panel.","presented_options":["Show recurring executions","Show recurring deliveries","Show delivery logs","Show aggregate level reporting"],"correct_options":["Show recurring executions"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"When using the In-App delivery channel workflow activity, This option allows you to target Adobe Campaign profiles who have subscribed to your mobile application and to personalize In-App messages with profile attributes available in Campaign.","presented_options":["Target users based on their Campaign profile (inAppProfile)","Target all users of a Mobile app (inAppBroadcast)","Target users based on their Mobile profile (inApp)"],"correct_options":["Target users based on their Campaign profile (inAppProfile)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"When using the In-App delivery channel workflow activity, This option allows you to send a message to all users of your mobile application even if they don't have an existing profile in Campaign.","presented_options":["Target all users of a Mobile app (inAppBroadcast)","Target users based on their Mobile profile (inApp)","Target users based on their Campaign profile (inAppProfile)"],"correct_options":["Target all users of a Mobile app (inAppBroadcast)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"When using the In-App delivery channel workflow activity, This option allows you to target all users of a mobile app that have a mobile profile in Campaign whether known or unknown and to personalize In-App messages with any profile attributes that have been obtained from mobile device.","presented_options":["Target users based on their Mobile profile (inApp)","Target all users of a Mobile app (inAppBroadcast)"],"correct_options":["Target users based on their Mobile profile (inApp)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"This workgroup section is for activities that let you manipulate data.","presented_options":["Data management (ETL)","Channel activities","Execution activities","Targeting activities"],"correct_options":["Data management (ETL)"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This data management workflow activity  can be used after importing a file in order to insert the data recovered into the Adobe Campaign database. ","presented_options":["Update data","Extract File","External API","Subscription Services","Incremental Query"],"correct_options":["Update data"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Complete the sentence below by filling in the blank.  When utilizing the Update data activity and performing an Insert Only operation, you can select this option _______ if the data imported contains certain records that already exist in the database to avoid any possible errors.","presented_options":["Generate an outbound transition for rejects","Ignore duplicates","Dedup on Insert","Ignore error conditions","Upsert as necessary"],"correct_options":["Generate an outbound transition for rejects"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This data management workflow activity allows you to import data in one structured form to use this data in Adobe Campaign. The data is temporarily imported and another activity is necessary to definitively integrate it in the Adobe Campaign database.","presented_options":["Load file","Update Data","External API","Incremental Query"],"correct_options":["Load file"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Load file data management activity supports hierarchical data structues for loading data, such as JSON & XML insead of flat file structures like .txt & .csv formats. ","presented_options":["False","True"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"In the Load file data management activity, if the file that you want to load the data from is compressed into a GZIP file (.gz), You can select the Decompression option in the Add a pre-processing step field. This allows you to unzip the file before loading the data. This option is only available if the file comes from the activity's inbound transition.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"In the Load file data management activity, the 'Keep the rejects in a file' option enables you to download a file containing errors that occurred during the import, and to apply to it a post-processing stage. When the option is activated, the outbound transition is renamed as 'Rejects'.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"This data management workflow activity allows you to receive or send files, test whether there are files present, or list files in Adobe Campaign.","presented_options":["Transfer file","External API","Query","Enrichment","Update data"],"correct_options":["Transfer file"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When using the Transfer file datamanagement workflow activity, the protocols available for selection are: ","presented_options":["HTTP","SFTP","Amazon S3","Microsoft Azure Blob Storage","iMessenger","MMS","File(s) present on the Adobe Campaign Server"],"correct_options":["HTTP","SFTP","Amazon S3","Microsoft Azure Blob Storage","File(s) present on the Adobe Campaign Server"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This data management workflow activity allows you to link unidentified data to existing sources.","presented_options":["Reconciliation","External API","Query","Update data","Enrichment"],"correct_options":["Reconciliation"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This data management workflow activity allows you to export data from Adobe Campaign in the form of an external file.","presented_options":["Extract file","Exnternal API","Retrieve Data","Export Data","Query","Enrichment"],"correct_options":["Extract file"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The Extract file activity must be placed after a Query activity in order to be used.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"In the Extract activity,  you can zip the output file by selecting 'Compression' in the 'Add a pre-processing step' field. The output file will be compressed into a GZIP file (.gz).","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This data management workflow activity, allows you to take profiles in mass and subscribe them to a service or unsubscribe them from a service.   This particular activity is the only Adobe Campaign functionality which allows multiple profiles to be subscribed to or to be unsubscribed from a service in a single action.","presented_options":["Subscription Services","Query","External API","Load data","Enrichment"],"correct_options":["Subscription Services"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This data management workflow Activity brings data into the worflow from an external system via an HTTP API call.","presented_options":["External API","Subscription Services","Query","Load data","Enrichment"],"correct_options":["External API"],"exam_topics":["Workflow Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Upon Creating a Landing Page, the Landing Page Dashboard allows you to scroll to three default lanigng pages.  What are the they?","presented_options":["Main Page, Confirmation Page, Error Page","Home Page, Unsubscribe Page, Error Page","Home Page, Unsubscribe Page, Subscribe Page","Product Page, Subscribe Page, Profile Page"],"correct_options":["Main Page, Confirmation Page, Error Page"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When creating a Landing Page Template, what types are available to choose from?","presented_options":["Generic","Acquisition","Subscription to a service","Unsbuscription from a service","Blacklist","Home","Newsletter"],"correct_options":["Generic","Acquisition","Subscription to a service","Unsbuscription from a service","Blacklist"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"docs.adobe.com - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Email rendering is available in the pre-production & production instances.","presented_options":["False","True"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Test Profiles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"True or False, Email rendering Test Profiles are read-only and are provided out of the box.  Which means you cannot create your own or edit the existing ones. ","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Test Profiles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the main reasons a BP would use the Trap feature when setting up Test Profiles ?","presented_options":["Detect illegal use and distribution of profile data","Ensure deliveries are received by profiles","Send a copy of the delivery to management","Determine over-saturation","Test Unsubscribe service for a Landing Page"],"correct_options":["Detect illegal use and distribution of profile data","Ensure deliveries are received by profiles","Send a copy of the delivery to management"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Test Profiles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"True or False, By sending an email to a trap profile, the recipient is able to receive the final email delivery, but the trap delviery is not included in the delivery KPIs reported.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Test Profiles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"True or False, The Timeline does not display workflows since they do not have a start & end date.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Campaign Design and Management"],"question_source":"Creating Programs and  Campaigns - CUSTOM","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"True or False, When inserting links into an email, Mirror Page and Unsubscription links aren't tracked, but generate a Mirror Page click and an Unsuscribed click.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Using Email Designer"],"question_source":"Inserting Links into Email Content","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Start & End reporting time period for Program/Campaign dynamic reports will be set to which values?","presented_options":["Start date to the End date of the Program Campaign","Send date plus seven days","Last 30 days","Last 7 days","Last 90 days"],"correct_options":["Start date to the End date of the Program Campaign"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Reporting in ACS - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Start & End reporting time period for Delivery dynamic reports will be set to which values?","presented_options":["Send date plus seven days","Start date to the End date of the Program Campaign","Last 30 days","Last 7 days","Last 90 days"],"correct_options":["Send date plus seven days"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Reporting in ACS - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Start & End reporting time period for Campaign instance dynamic reports will be set to which values?","presented_options":["Last 30 days","Start date to the End date of the Program Campaign","Send date plus seven days","Last 7 days","Last 90 days"],"correct_options":["Last 30 days"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Reporting in ACS - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"True or False. Fatigue rules summary reports are available for deliveries, campaigns and programs.  These reports are static and cannot be edited.","presented_options":["True","False"],"correct_options":["True"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Reporting in ACS - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"As a BP, what is a reason you would include multiple Panels on a custom dynamic report you are building?","presented_options":["You want to present data on multiple time periods","You want to present data in different charts","You want to present data for mulitple programs","You want to present data for multiple deliveries"],"correct_options":["You want to present data on multiple time periods"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Dynamic Reports - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Within the structure of a freeform table, Metrics are: ","presented_options":["Measurements of the status of a message","Represent rows in the tracking logs","Represent rows in the broad logs","Represent rows in the delivery logs","Data types targeted for analysis"],"correct_options":["Measurements of the status of a message"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Dynamic Reports - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Data types targeted for analysis","question_text":"Within the structure of a freeform table, Dimensions are: ","presented_options":["Data types targeted for analysis","Represent rows in the tracking logs","Represent rows in the broad logs","Represent rows in the delivery logs","Measurements of the status of a message"],"correct_options":["Data types targeted for analysis"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Dynamic Reports - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When creating a Dynamic report, if you want to add a new Summary Number Visualization to the top of the report, you would have to :","presented_options":["Click on the Summary Heading in the free form table, then select Summary Number from visualization pallete and dragp/drop onto target area.","You cannot add new visualizations to custom dynamic reports.  You cannot change the preset Visualizations.","Drop the segment for the desired filter onto the visualization Summary Number in the pallete section."],"correct_options":["Click on the Summary Cell in the free form table heading, then select Summary Number from visualization pallete and dragp/drop onto target area."],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Dynamic Reports - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where would you go to view the list of scheduled reports for a dynamic report.","presented_options":["Within the dynamic Report -> Share Menu option- >  Scheduled Reports","Marketing Activiites - > Reports -> Select dynamic Report -> Scheduled Reports","Home -> Administration -> Reports -> Select Dynamic Report -> Schedule Reports","Reports -> Dynamic Reports - > Select Dynamic Report -> Scheduled Reports"],"correct_options":["Within the dynamic Report, select Share Menu option, Scheduled Reports"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Dynamic Reports - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The first step in planning for a direct mail campaign would be ?","presented_options":["Identify the direct mail providers requirements(file naming convention, structure & format of file, order of columns, sort order of data, File Transfer Method)","Obtain physical assets used in direct mail","Enable outbound direct mail option from Adminstration configuration section","Enable Direct Mail from Experience Cloud Administration","Obtain direct mail licensing for sending directly from ACS"],"correct_options":["Identify the direct mail providers requirements(file naming convention, structure & format of file, order of columns, sort order of data, File Transfer Method)"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Typology rules will exclude all profiles where the field ______ is not checked on the individual profile.  record","presented_options":["Address Specified","Include in Direct Mail","Enable for Direct Mail","Physical Address Specified"],"correct_options":["Address Specified"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"In order for a BP User to be able to export the file for creating direct mail deliveries, what role has to be added to the user's permissions?","presented_options":["Direct Mail","External API","FILE TRANSFER","File Admin","Administrator","EXPORT"],"correct_options":["EXPORT"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Fill in the blank.  When setting up a Direct Mail Campaign, the prepare action will fail if _______  has not been configured.","presented_options":["Schedule","Seed","Audience Idenitifer Key","Confirmation Email Address","Outbound Postal Address"],"correct_options":["Schedule"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"At which step in the Direct mail Creation process are both the Typology Rules & Analyzes the Target Audience done?","presented_options":["Prepare the delivery","Conifgure the Schedule","Set Properties","Define the Content","Specify Audience","Transfer the File"],"correct_options":["Prepare the delivery"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"The following are options for sending the extraction file to a Direct Mail Provider: ","presented_options":["Regular Email, with file attached","Via Campaign workflow, using Transfer file Activity","Uploading manually to Shared drive such as FTP or Amazon S3 bucket","Download, print and mail to provider","Download, Print and send to Audience Address list","Via workflow, using Push file Activity"],"correct_options":["Regular Email, with file attached","Via Campaign workflow, using Transfer file Activity","Uploading manually to Shared drive such as FTP or Amazon S3 bucket"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"When validating a delivery deployment, the Exclusion Causes tab has the following causes as deafults: ","presented_options":["Address not specified(AddressUndefined)","Blacklisted address (Blacklisted)","Quarantined address (Quarantine)","Duplicate (Duplicate)","Mailbox Full (MailboxFull)","Unknown Recipient(Unknown)"],"correct_options":["Address not specified(AddressUndefined)","Blacklisted address (Blacklisted)","Quarantined address (Quarantine)","Duplicate (Duplicate)"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct Mail Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"The following are valid SMS delivery Types","presented_options":["Single-send","Recurring","Immediate","EMS/MMS","Plain/Text","Push"],"correct_options":["Single-send","Recurring"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Recurring SMS messages can only be done via ________ ","presented_options":["a workflow","the admin console","the Experience Cloud","Marketing Activity pages"],"correct_options":["a workflow"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Recurring SMS frequency is setup and defined by __________","presented_options":["Scheduler workflow activity","a BP with the workflow administration Role","Any Campaign Standard user with access to marketing activities","The schdule Tab on the Recurring SMS Page"],"correct_options":["Scheduler workflow activity"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"To deliver SMS messages to the targeted audiences, the targeted audience must have ________- ","presented_options":["Profile records with mobile numbers","Profile record with enable SMS set to true","either Verizon, ATT or T-Mobile."],"correct_options":["Profile records with mobile numbers"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"Ture or False.   You must be an SMS administrator in order to create custom SMS Templates.","presented_options":["False","True"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"SMS messages can contain: ","presented_options":["Text based content, personalization, content blocks, dynamic text","Text based content only","Text based content & personalized content only","Text based content & dynamic text only"],"correct_options":["Text based content, personalization, content blocks, dynamic text"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What is done during  the prepare delivery step of an SMS Message?","presented_options":["Apply typology rules","Analyzes the target","Inserts Personalization","A sample proof message is sent","An SMS rendering message is sent","A mirror page is created with SMS message"],"correct_options":["Apply typology rules","Analyzes the target","Inserts Personalization"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Where would an Administrator go to set the SMS Sender number?","presented_options":["Administration -> Channels -> SMS -> SMS accounts -> Mblox(defaultSmsBulk) -> SMPP Channel Settings -> Source number","Experience Cloud - > Application Settings ->  Mobile Account -> Source Number","SMS Sender attribute on SMS Page"],"correct_options":["Administration -> Channels -> SMS -> SMS accounts -> Mblox(defaultSmsBulk) -> SMPP Channel Settings -> Source number"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Direct SMS Campaign - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"When a profile has a preferred language set, but that language Vairant was not setup for the delivery, the Receipient will receive ?","presented_options":["The delivery's default language variant","An A/B Language Testing the language variant","The language assigned to the most profiles"],"correct_options":["The delivery's default language variant"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Multilingual Campaigns","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Multilingual deliveries can be created from ….","presented_options":["The Home Page","The Marketing activiites page","A Campaign","A workflow","All the above"],"correct_options":["All the above"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Overview of Multilingual Campaigns","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Fill in the blank.   _________ provides the ability to create and manage newsletters and cross channel communicaitons.","presented_options":["Services","Programs","Sub-Programs","Campaigns","Enrichment Activities within a workflow"],"correct_options":["Services"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Services and Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Services can only send messages to profiles who ________","presented_options":["are subscribed to the service","have services enabled set to true","have yet to subscribe to a service","have performed a transactional event on a channel"],"correct_options":["are subscribed to the service"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Services and Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Each Service comes with: ","presented_options":["Subscription (opt-in) and unsubscription(opt out) mechanisms","Subscription and/or unsubscription confirmation mechanisms","Subscription History","Test profiles enabled for each delivery","a dedicated workflow for saving audiences","a dedicated workflow to trigger re-engagement activities"],"correct_options":["Subscription (opt-in) and unsubscription(opt out) mechanisms","Subscription and/or unsubscription confirmation mechanisms","Subscription History"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Services and Landing Pages - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"True-False","question_text":"The out-of-the-box Landing Page Structure consists of three pages: Main, Confirmation and Error.  A BP can add or remove Landing pages as necessary to the structure.","presented_options":["False","True"],"correct_options":["False"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Creating Landing Pgaes - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The Steps to create an Import template are: ","presented_options":["Duplicate Import Template -> Upload Sample Data File -> Customize workflow - > Set Template to Available","Create a new Import Template -> Upload Sample Data File -> Customize workflow - > Set Template to Available","Create new  Import Template -> Customize workflow -> Upload Sample Data File - > Set Template to Available","Duplicate Import Template -> Upload Sample Data File - > Set Template to Available","Create new Import Template -> Upload Sample Data File - > Set Template to Available"],"correct_options":["Duplicate Import Template -> Upload Sample Data File -> Customize workflow - > Set Template to Available"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Import Template: Creating an Import Template - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"Name the two out of the box templates provided for Import templates.","presented_options":["Import data(simplifiedImport)","Import into an audience(simplifiedImportWithAudience)","Import into Extraction File(simplefiedImportExtract)","Import into Transfer File(simplifiedImportTransfer)"],"correct_options":["Import data(simplifiedImport)","Import into an audience(simplifiedImportWithAudience)"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Import Template: Creating an Import Template - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What are the 3 Event Statuses(not including error statuses)","presented_options":["Pending","Processing","Processed","New","Archived","Published"],"correct_options":["Pending","Processing","Processed"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Making an Event API Call","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"What is a reason that the open counts in a dynamic report would not match the database count?","presented_options":["Heuristics are used in Dynamic reporting to track opens, even when the open action cannot be tracked.","The Dynamic Report Aggregator service has yet to be run","The report is custom and the filter has not been applied properly","There is a 1 hour lag from Open to inclusion on the reports"],"correct_options":["Heuristics are used in Dynamid reporting to track opens, even when the open action cannot be tracked."],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"What is the reason N/A can sometimes appear in dynamic reports?","presented_options":["Delivery has been deleted and shows N/A to not cause discepancy in the results","This can occur when dragging/dropping the delivery dimension onto the report and the report fetches all deliveries, even if they are not transactional","A user has selected an invalid reporting period","The data retuned is taking too long to query the results"],"correct_options":["Delivery has been deleted and shows N/A to not cause discepancy in the results","This can occur when dragging/dropping the delivery dimension onto the report and the report fetches all deliveries, even if they are not transactional"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________ Report  details the overall hard and soft errors encountered during deliveries as well as the automatic processing of bounces.  This report inluces Flop 5 repartition which lists five deliveries with highest number of quarantines.  In addition the rerport also includes Bounce reasons talbe for errors that cause bounces for each delivery","presented_options":["Bounce Summary","Complaints","Delivery Summary","Non-deliverables and bounces"],"correct_options":["Bounce Summary"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________ Report  contains the performance data for each domain represented in the audience for an email delivery. If it is a campaign or program report, the performance data is available for multiple audiences. This data allows you to analyze the behavior of each domain in reaction to specific events.This report includes Boradcast statistics which contans the available data for possible errors encountered with each domain.  The report also contains Tracking statistics which contains avalable data for recipient reactivity to the delivery (delivered, open, click, unsubscribed, Mirror page, blacklisted)","presented_options":["Breakdown by domains","Delivery Summary","Delivery Throughput","Tracking indicators","Hot clicks"],"correct_options":["Breakdown by domains"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ______ Report identifies the deliveries that have received the most declarations as spam.   This report features tables which will display the number of recipients that have declared the email as spam or junk.","presented_options":["Complaints","Breakdown by domains","Delivery Summary","Delivery Throughput","Tracking indicators","Hot clicks"],"correct_options":["Complaints"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ______ Report details the main information relative to an email, or several emails.This report will show Delivery Statistics table with Processed/Sent, Deliverd, Bounces+ Errors.  The report will also show Opens and Clicks table with click, open, Unique Opens, and Unique Clicks","presented_options":["Delivery Summary","Breakdown by domains","Delivery Throughput","Tracking indicators","Hot clicks"],"correct_options":["Delivery Summary"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ______ Report contains data relating to the delivery throughput of a send, or several sends. It provides:This report will show: the number of messages processed per hour, The Top 5 deliveries table and complementary summary numbers that show the five deliveries with the best gain in retries.","presented_options":["Delivery Throughput","Delivery Summary","Breakdown by domains","Tracking indicators","Hot clicks"],"correct_options":["Delivery Throughput"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The bounce reason ________ is for the type of error generated when a delivery is sent to an invalid email address.","presented_options":["User unknown","Invalid domain","Unreachable","Account disabled","Mailbox full","Not connected"],"correct_options":["User unknown"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Bounce Summary Report- Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The bounce reason ________ is for the type of error generated when a delivery is sent to an email address whose domain is wrong or no longer exists.","presented_options":["Invalid domain","User unknown","Unreachable","Account disabled","Mailbox full","Not connected"],"correct_options":["Invalid domain"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Bounce Summary Report- Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The bounce reason ________ is for an error encountered in the message delivery string, such as domain temporarily unreachable.","presented_options":["Unreachable","Invalid domain","User unknown","Account disabled","Mailbox full","Not connected"],"correct_options":["Unreachable"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Bounce Summary Report- Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The bounce reason ________ is for the type of error generated when a delivery is sent to an email address that no longer exists.","presented_options":["Account disabled","Invalid domain","User unknown","Unreachable","Mailbox full","Not connected"],"correct_options":["Account disabled"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Bounce Summary Report- Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The bounce reason ________ is for the type of error generated when when the recipient's inbox is full. There are five attempts to deliver the message before this error is generated.","presented_options":["Mailbox full","Invalid domain","User unknown","Unreachable","Account disabled","Not connected"],"correct_options":["Mailbox full"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Bounce Summary Report- Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The bounce reason ________ is for the type of error generated when the recipient's mobile phone is off or it is not connected to a network at the time the message is sent.","presented_options":["Not connected","Invalid domain","User unknown","Unreachable","Account disabled","Mailbox full"],"correct_options":["Not connected"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Bounce Summary Report- Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________  report provides details related to In-App deliveries.  This report will show Processed/Sent, Delivered, Impressions, Unique Impressions, In-App Click Thorugh rate, IN-App Dismissal rate","presented_options":["In-App","Push Notifications","Delivery Throughput","Delivery Summary"],"correct_options":["In-App"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________  report provides details on all the errors encountered during a delivery.  This report will show Processed/Sent, Delivered, Soft Bounce, Hard Bounce, Bounces + Errors, & Breakdown by Domain","presented_options":["Non-deliverables and bounces","Complaints","Bounce Summary","Delivery Summary"],"correct_options":["Non-deliverables and bounces"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________ report identifies the deliveries that have been most viewed by recipients.   This report will show tables/charts that break down the number of recipients who opened email based on Browser, Device, Platform and Domain","presented_options":["Opens","Hot Clicks","Service Summary","URLs and Click Streams","Delivery Summary"],"correct_options":["Opens"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________  report will help you understand how users interact with push notifications, mobile applications and deliveries.  This report will show Processed/Sent, Delivered, Impressions, Unique Impressions, click through rate, and Open rate","presented_options":["Push notifcation","In-App","Opens","Delivery Summary","In-App delivery"],"correct_options":["Push notifcation"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________ report provides details about SMS deliveries, such as delivered and bounce rates.  This report will show Processed/Sent, Delivered, and Bounces + Errors(# of emails that could not be delivered)","presented_options":["SMS","In-App","Push notification","Delivery summary report","SMS Delivery & Bounce"],"correct_options":["SMS"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"The ________ report contains the key indicators for tracking behavior after email messages are received.  This report will show Delivered, Open, Click, Unsubscribed, Spam and clicks on Mirror Page","presented_options":["Tracking indicators","Opens","Delivery Summary","URLs and Click Streams"],"correct_options":["Tracking indicators"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________ report identifies the deliveries with the most unsubscriptions.","presented_options":["Unsubscriptions","Complaints","Bounce Summary","Blacklisted"],"correct_options":["Unsubscriptions"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ________ report shows the URLs that were clicked the most during a delivery, or several deliveries if they are linked to a campaign or program.  This report inlcudes a Most Visited Links table containing the available data for recipient behavior per delivery such as Click & Unique Clicks","presented_options":["URLs and click streams","Hot Clicks","Delivery Summary","Opens","Trakcing indicators"],"correct_options":["URLs and click streams"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The _______ report presents the message content (HTML and/or text) with the percentage of clicks on each link.","presented_options":["Hot clicks","URLs and click streams","Delivery Summary"],"correct_options":["Hot clicks"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"If you created dynamic content for your delivery, you can view the percentages for each condition that you defined when using the _______ report.","presented_options":["Hot clicks","URLs and click streams","Delivery Summary"],"correct_options":["Hot clicks"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The ______ report details the evolution of subscriptions and unsubscriptions of your service. This report is only accessible from your Service page via the advanced menu Profiles & Audiences > Services .","presented_options":["Service Summary","Hot clicks","URLs and click streams","Delivery Summary"],"correct_options":["Service Summary"],"exam_topics":["Using Reports"],"question_source":"Using Reports Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"The length of SMS messages is restricted to ____ characters if it is in GSM encoding and only ____ characters if it is in Unicode","presented_options":["160  - 70","160 - 320","160 - 80","255 - 128"],"correct_options":["160  - 70"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"SMS - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Multi Answer","question_text":"To deliver SMS messages to a mobile telephone you need: ","presented_options":["A Routing external account configured on the Mobile (SMS) channel with the Bulk delivery mode.","A delivery template that is correctly linked to this external account.","An Experience Cloud Push Service Enabled","A Push-woosh Account created & configured in cloud configuration","An Amazon SMS Service enabled via cloud configuration"],"correct_options":["A Routing external account configured on the Mobile (SMS) channel with the Bulk delivery mode.","A delivery template that is correctly linked to this external account."],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"SMS - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This security role ________ has the right to run publications and create custom resources.","presented_options":["Datamodel","Administration","Generic import","Workflow","Prepare deliveries"],"correct_options":["Datamodel"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Administration Roles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This security role ________ has the generic administration right.","presented_options":["Administration","Datamodel","Generic import","Workflow","Prepare deliveries"],"correct_options":["Administration"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Administration Roles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This security role ________ has the Right to run a generic import on data. For this to work, you need to link the______  role to the Workflow role.","presented_options":["Generic import","Datamodel","Administration","Workflow","Prepare deliveries"],"correct_options":["Generic import"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Administration Roles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This security role ________ has the right to create, modify, prepare and delete deliveries. Users with this role can prepare the delivery but not send it.","presented_options":["Prepare deliveries","Datamodel","Start deliveries","Administration","Workflow"],"correct_options":["Prepare deliveries"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Administration Roles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This security role ________ has the right to create, modify, prepare, send, and delete deliveries.","presented_options":["Start deliveries","Prepare deliveries","Datamodel","Workflow","Generic Import"],"correct_options":["Start deliveries"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Administration Roles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"This security role ________ has the right to manage the execution of workflows (start, stop, pause etc.). Users with this role can not send a delivery even in a workflow","presented_options":["Workflow","Start deliveries","Prepare deliveries","Datamodel","Adminstration"],"correct_options":["Workflow"],"exam_topics":["Administration"],"question_source":"Administration Roles - Custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Asnwer","question_text":"The ________  feature is an alert management system that enables a group of users to automatically receive notifications containing information on the execution of their deliveries.   The notification sent contains a report based on defualt criteria Deliveries with : failed preparation, soft bounce error ration, hard bounce error ratio, pending status longer than usual, low throughput, and in progress.","presented_options":["Delivery alerting","Delivery Report Dashboard","Sending Failure alert","Bounce alerting"],"correct_options":["Delivery alerting"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Receiving Alerts when Failures happen - custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}, 
{
"question_type":"Single Answer","question_text":"Once a delivery is sent, the ________  for a delivery, allows you to view the delivery status for each profile and the associated failure type and reason ","presented_options":["Sending logs tab","Log tab","Tracking Logs tab","Delivery tab"],"correct_options":["Sending logs tab"],"exam_topics":["Delivery Management"],"question_source":"Understanding delivery failures - custom","chosen_options": [],"IsAnswered": false,"IsCorrect": false,"IsInReviewMode": false
}

   ]
}